<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fitness on Steve Leonard</title>
    <link>https://www.xsleonard.com/tags/fitness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fitness on Steve Leonard</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.xsleonard.com/tags/fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Designing a home gym</title>
      <link>https://www.xsleonard.com/designing-a-home-gym/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.xsleonard.com/designing-a-home-gym/</guid>
      <description>A home gym contains essential equipment for productive workouts. Due to space, this excludes all machines, which aren&amp;rsquo;t necessary for most people anyway. Home gym workouts focus on free-weight (barbells and dumbbells) and bodyweight exercises.
The basic equipment  Power rack Bench Barbell Plates Dumbbells Accessories Flooring Maintenance Other Equipment  Power Rack Not all power racks have a pull-up bar across the top of the frame, or they may have poorly shaped pegs for pull-up exercises that will constrain your hand positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Diet</title>
      <link>https://www.xsleonard.com/how-to-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.xsleonard.com/how-to-diet/</guid>
      <description>The rules of dieting are simple and easy to follow once you get an accurate idea of food and your body. This is a general guide to dieting, aimed at inexperienced or struggling dieters.
Measure your food When I was dieting seriously for the first time, I realized how wrong I was about estimating food. After I weighed some of my meals and made rough calculations of how many calories I was eating each day, it was obvious why I was overweight.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
